Register of the Russell Gerard Davis Papers, 1949-1988.
Hoover Institution Archives
Russell Gerard Davis Papers,
1949-1988.
81033
Davis, Russell G.
32 manuscript boxes, 1 card file box (13.8 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Studies, reports, statistics, and memoranda, relating to education and economic development in underdeveloped countries.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1981.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Access Points
United States. Agency for International Development.; Education.; Developing countries.; Education--Developing countries.
Biographical Note
1922, October 29 Born, Hopkinton, Massachusetts
1955 Ed.D., Harvard University
1955-1957 Education adviser, U.S. Agency for International Development, Ethiopia
1960-1962 Education planning adviser, Latin America
1966- Professor of education and development, Harvard University
1966 Author, Planning Human Resource Development
1969 Author, Build a Mill, Build a City, Build a School
1975 Author, Education and Employment
Series Description
- Projected Monographs. (Box No. 1-6.)
  Drafts of projected monographs by Russell G. Davis and others, relating to education planning and development in underdeveloped countries, 1977-1979. Arranged alphabetically by author or editor.
- Country Reports. (Box No. 6-18.)
  Reports by Russell G. Davis and others, relating to education planning and development in specific countries, 1967-1980. Arranged alphabetically by country.
- General Reports. (Box No. 18-23.)
  Reports by Russell G. Davis and others, relating to education planning and development in general, 1969-1980. Arranged alphabetically by author.
- Miscellany. (Box No. 23.)
  Fragments of unidentified writings, and supporting materials for unidentified writings. Arranged alphabetically by form.
- Card File. (Box No. 24.)
  Index card bibliographies and supporting materials for unidentified writings. Unarranged.
Container List
- PROJECTED MONOGRAPHS
  - Davis, Russell G., "Manpower Planning Methods," 1978
    - Unit I (Box 1., Folder 1)
    - Unit II (Folder 2)
    - Unit III (Folder 3)
    - Unit IV (Folder 4)
  - Davis, Russell G., and Noel F. McGinn, ed., "Analysis in Support of Educational Planning: A State of the Art Appraisal," 1977
    - Foreword (Folder 5)
    - Chapter 1. Davis, Russell G., Barclay Hudson, and Gary Lewis, "Educational Planning: Notes on State of the Art" (Folder 6-7)
    - Chapter 3. McGinn, Noel F., "Information Requirements for Educational Planning" (Folder 8)
    - Chapter 5. Snodgrass, Donald R., with Debabrata Sen, "Manpower Planning Analysis in Developing Countries: The State of the Art" (Folder 9)
    - Chapter 7. Prysor-Jones, Suzanne, "Education and Equality in Developing Countries" (Folder 10)
    - Chapter 8. Harman, David, "Nonformal Education in Developing Countries: An Analytical Survey of Some Programs and Approaches" (Folder 11)
    - Chapter 9. Murerwa, H. Muchemwa, "Nonformal Education and the Employment of Youth: A Review of the Role of Training Programs in Generating Employment for Rural Youth in Africa" (Box 2., Folder 1)
    - Chapter 10. Kline, David, "Planning Nonformal Education: Some Comments on Methods and Information Requirements" (Folder 2)
    - Chapter 11. Picker, Hans, "The State of the Art of Education Relevance Assessment" (Folder 3)
  - Kline, David, "Basic Empirical Research and Evaluation Methods for Educational Policy and Planning: A Set of Instructional Packages," 1978
    - Bound copy (Folder 4-5)
    - Instructional Package I. "The Relation of Educational Research and Educational Planning (Box 3., Folder 1)
    - Instructional Package II. "Problem Identification and Formulation" (Folder 2)
    - Instructional Package III. "Guidelines for Selecting a Research Method" (Folder 3)
    - Instructional Package IV. "Planning and Conducting Educational Research" (Folder 4)
    - Instructional Package V. "Selecting the Subjects: Sampling (All Ages)" (Folder 5)
    - Instructional Package VI. "Research Method I: Surveys" (Folder 6)
    - Instructional Package VII. "Research Method II: Experiments" (Box 4., Folder 1)
    - Instructional Package VIII. "Research Method III: Naturalistic Inquiry" (Folder 2)
    - Instructional Package IX. "Research Method IV: Evaluation Research" (Folder 3)
    - Instructional Package X. "Research Method V: Cost-Evaluation Techniques" (Folder 4)
    - Graphs (Folder 5)
    - Readings (Box 5., Folder 1)
    - Miscellany (Folder 2)
  - "Techniques of Educational Planning: Systems Models and Methods," n.d. (Folder 3)
    - Introduction
    - Chapter 1. "Systems Models and Methods for Educational Planning: Unit One" (Folder 4)
    - Chapter 2. "Systems Models and Methods for Educational Planning: Unit Two" (Folder 5)
  - Untitled work on educational planning, n.d.
    - Outline (Folder 6)
    - Chapter 1. Davis, Russell G., and Barclay Hudson, "Planning Education for Development: Basic Issues" (Folder 7)
    - Chapter 2. Davis, Russell G., and Barclay Hudson, "Planning Education for Development: Further to Basic Issues" (Folder 8)
    - Chapter 3. Davis, Russell G., "The Social Demand Approach to Educational Planning" (Folder 9)
    - Chapter 4. Davis, Russell G., "The Manpower Requirements Approach to Educational Planning" (Folder 10)
    - Chapter 5. Barrios, Maritza, and Russell G. Davis, "The Rate-of-Return Approach to Educational Planning" (Folder 11)
    - Chapter 6. McGinn, Noel, and Ernesto Schiefelbein, "Comprehensive Planning for Educational Reform: A Case Study of Chile, 1965-1970" (Folder 12)
    - Chapter 7. Davis, Russell G., "Comprehensive Planning Models: A Commentary on Policy and Program Issues" (Folder 13)
    - Chapter 8. Prysor-Jones, Suzanne, "Education and Equality in Developing Countries" (Folder 14)
    - Chapter 9. Snodgrass, Donald R., "The Distribution of Schooling and the Distribution of Income" (Folder 15)
    - Chapter 10. Davis, Russell G., "Linking Education and Work: Background Issues for Planning" (Folder 16)
    - Chapter 11. Davis, Russell G., "Employment and Continuing Education: A Case Study of Self-Employment Training" (Folder 17)
    - Chapter 12. Welsh, Thomas, "Goals and National Purpose in Planning" (Folder 18)
    - Chapter 13. Beardsley, John, "Beneficiary Participation in Rural Education Programs: Planning Issues" (Folder 19)
    - Chapter 14. Davis, Russell G., "Broad Trend Analysis and Planning: Toward Alternate Futures" (Folder 20)
    - Chapter 15. McGinn, Noel, "Themes and Issues in the Use of Research for Educational Planning" (Box 6., Folder 1.)
    - Chapter 16. Warwick, Donald, "Integrating Planning and Implementation: A Transactional Approach" (Folder 2)
  - Untitled work on nonformal education, 1979
    - Modular Package II. Kline, David, "Information Needs and Information Systems for Planning Nonformal Education" (Folder 3)
    - Modular Package II (revised version). Kline, David, "Policy Issues and Objectives for Nonformal Education" (Folder 4)
    - Modular Package V. Harman, David, "Planning Nonformal Education: Instructional Methods and Design" (Folder 5)
    - Modular Package VII. Kline, David, "Information Systems to Support the Planning and Evaluation of Nonformal Education" (Folder 6)
  - Untitled work on statistical analysis, n.d.
    - Chapter 1. Lewis, Gary, "Categories of Analysis Techniques" (Folder 7)
    - Chapter 2. Lewis, Gary, "Visual Data Displays" (Folder 8)
    - Chapter 3. Lewis, Gary, "Tables of Counts" (Folder 9)
    - Chapter 5. Lewis, Gary, "Regression Analysis" (Folder 10)
    - Chapter 6. McGinn, Noel, and Ernesto Schiefelbein, "How Educational Statistics Can Be Utilized for Policy Analysis: A Case Study" (Folder 11)
- COUNTRY REPORTS
  - Afghanistan (Box 6.)
    - Davis, Russell G.
      - "The Feasibility of Developing Analysis to Support Educational Planning in Afghanistan," 1976 (Folder 12)
      - "A Preliminary Study of the Information and Analysis Capacity Necessary for Developing a Sector Assessment: Afghanistan Case," 1978 (Folder 13)
      - Miscellany (Folder 14)
    - Africa. Henry, David D., untitled report, n.d. (Folder 15)
    - Asia
      - Davis, Russell G., "Indicators for Changing Educational Objectives and Targets in Asian Countries," n.d. (Folder 16)
      - Miscellany (Folder 17)
    - Bolivia (Folder 18)
      - Bolivia, "Educational Management and Instructional Development: Request for Proposals," 1974
      - Morawetz, David, "The Fate of the Least Developed Member of an LDC Integration Scheme: Bolivia in the Andean Group," 1979 (Folder 19)
    - Botswana (Box 7.)
      - Agar, Jenny, Joyce Moock, and David Kline, "A Non Formal Education Information System for Botswana," 1977 (Folder 1)
      - Locey, Michael H., "Information Storage and Retrieval: Technical Report, Non-Formal Education Database, Botswana, Africa," 1977 (Folder 2)
      - Murerwa, Herbert Muchemwa
        - "Botswana Trip Report," 1977 (Folder 3)
        - "The Design of Educational Training Programs to Generate Rural Youth Employment: A Case Study of Three Brigade Programs in Botswana," n.d. (Folder 4)
        - "Nonformal Education and Work: A General Perspective, and the Case of the Botswana Brigades," 1978 (Folder 5-6)
  - Brazil. Sander, Benno, David K. Kline, and Russell G. Davis, Formalismo Educacional en los Paises en Desarrollo: El Caso Brasileno, 1974 (Folder 7)
  - Chile
    - "The Chilean Educational Reform: Cases, Commentary and Analysis," n.d.
      - Introduction. "Education in a Stagnating Society" (Folder 8)
      - Case 2. "The Plan for the North: What Went Wrong?" (Folder 9)
      - Case 3. "Planning to Plan: Or, Should There Be a Planning Office?" (Folder 10)
      - Case 5. "Administrative Power: Or, the Utility of Rules" (Folder 11)
      - Case 6. "Planning to Get Schools Built" (Folder 12)
      - Case 7. "The Debate on Automatic Promotion" (Folder 13)
      - Case 8. "Changing the Structure and Content of Primary and Secondary Education" (Folder 14)
      - Case 9. "Inducing Change in Teacher Behavior" (Folder 15)
      - Case 10. "The Training of Teachers for a New Education" (Box 8., Folder 1)
      - Case 11. "Salary Increass for Teachers" (Folder 2)
      - Case 12. "Participatory Planning in Teacher Assignment" (Folder 3)
      - Case 14. "He Who Pays the Piper..." (Folder 4)
      - Case 15. "The New Reading Program" (Folder 5)
      - Case 16. "Educational Television" (Folder 6)
      - Miscellany (Folder 7)
    - Davis, Russell G., "Manpower Planning in Chile: The Basic Method Applied," 1978 (Folder 8)
    - McGinn, Noel, and Ernesto Schiefelbein, "Contribution of Planning to Educational Reform: A Case Study of Chile, 1965-1970," 1979 (Folder 9)
    - Schiefelbein, Ernesto, and Russell G. Davis, Development of Educational Planning Models and Application in the Chilean School Reform, 1974 (Folder 10)
    - Toro B., Ernesto, "Acerca de la Transferencia de Experiencias de Educacion y Cambio Social: Aportes del Provecto Aprendizaje: Chile," 1980 (Folder 11)
  - Colombia
    - Coes, Donald V., "Input/Output and Linear Programming Techniques for Employment Analysis in Colombia," 1972 (Folder 12)
    - Daines, Samuel R., "Summary Results of Employment, Income Distribution and Small Farm Analysis," 1972 (Folder 13)
  - Dominican Republic
    - "Bases de Una Politica del Desarrollo de Mano de Obra: Demanda, Oferta y Tendencias del Mercado de Trabajo en la Republica Dominicana, 1970-1985," n.d. (Folder 14)
    - Davis, Russell G., "Manpower Planning with an Alternative Method I: The Dominican Republic Case," 1979
      - English version (Folder 15)
      - Spanish version (Folder 16)
    - Education Development Center, "Los Recursos Humanos y el Empleo en la Republica Dominicana," n.d. Vol. II, "Documentos de Trabajo" (Box 9., Folder 1-2)
  - Ecuador
    - Ecuador. Ministerio de Educacion, "Analisis del Sector Educativo en el Ecuador," 1974 (Folder 3)
    - Robinson, Brandon, "The Ecuadorean Education Sector Analysis: A Brief Description of the Methodology," 1973
  - El Salvador. See Salvador
  - Ethiopia. "Policy Statement of the New Council of Ministers," 1974 (Folder 5)
  - Guatemala
    - "Morphological Analysis of the System and Organizational Structure of Education at the National and Regional Levels: The Case of Guatemala in 1975," n.d. (Folder 6)
    - Miscellany (Folder 7)
  - India
    - Davis, Russell G., "Small Business and Employment Creation in Calcutta: The CYSEC Case," 1978 (Folder 8)
    - "Sectoral Plan: Education," n.d. (Folder 9)
  - Kenya. Smock, Audrey Chapman, "Education and Career Patterns in the Public Service Sector in Kenya," 1978 (Folder 10)
  - Latin America
    - Blair, Philip M., "Comments on Education Sector Analysis," 1974 Evaluation in Six Latin American Countries," n.d. (Folder 11)
    - Daniere, Andre, "The Education Sector Assessment: (Box 10., Folder 1)
    - Hutchinson, Edmond, Charles Montrie, Lawrence Posner, and William Charleson, "Intercountry Evaluation of Education Sector Programs: Brazil, Colombia, Panama," 1976 (Folder 2)
    - McGinn, Noel, "Universidad Reformada," n.d. (Folder 3)
    - Robinson, Brandon
      - "A Brief Description of an Education Sector Analysis Methodology," 1973 (Folder 4)
      - "Experimentation in Instructional Processes to Lower Education Unit Output Cost," 1972 (Folder 5)
      - "National Decisions and Foreign Assistance," 1972 (Folder 6)
      - "Questions and Answers Concerning Methodological Working Document #19, 'A Brief Description of an Education Sector Analysis Methodology,'" 1973 (Folder 7)
      - "Some Special Problems and Characteristics of an Education Sector Analysis," 1973 (Folder 8)
      - "What Is Sector Analysis?" 1974 (Folder 9)
    - Rogers, Daniel, and Dean Jamison, "Economics and Educational Technology in the United States (And References to Other Countries)," 1973 (Folder 10)
    - "The Sector Approach: Education: Interim Guidelines for the Preparation of a Sector Analysis, a Sector Strategy and a Sector Loan," n.d. (Folder 11)
    - Computer data printout (Folder 12)
    - Miscellany (Folder 13)
  - Lesotho
    - "Evaluation Report on the Literacy Schools Experiment LDTC, 1979," 1980 (Folder 14)
    - Lesotho Distance Teaching Centre, "Literacy and Numeracy for Life: The Use of Distance Teaching Methods to Help Rural Basotho Improve Their Literacy and Numeracy Skills," 1979 "Upper Secondary Education in Malaysia: Access and Enrollment Policy and Analysis of Effectiveness," 1978 (Folder 15)
    - Malaysia. Harvard Institute for International Development, "Upper Secondary Education in Malaysia: Access and Enrollment Policy and Analysis of Effectiveness," 1978 (Box 11., Folder 1)
  - Mauritania
    - Beardsley, John R., "Report on Mission to Mauritania: Observations and Recommendations," 1977 (Folder 2)
    - Daniere, Andre
      - "Education, Training and Employment Generation in Mauritania," 1977 (Folder 3)
      - "Harvard Mission to Mauritania and Upper Volta and Strategy for Implementation of the AID/Harvard Mandate in Planning Evaluation and Assistance," 1977 (Folder 4)
  - Mexico
    - Davis, Russell G., Scientific, Engineering and Technical Education in Mexico, 1967 (Folder 5)
    - Vielle D., Jean Pierre, "Planaecion y Reforma de la Educacion Superior (1970-1976)," 1976 (Folder 6)
  - Pakistan. "Draft Outline of Sector Assessment for Pakistan," n.d. (Folder 7)
  - Paraguay
    - Daniere, Andre, "Estudio de la Demanda de Mano de Obra: Plan y Descripcion del Trabajo," 1978 (Folder 8)
    - McGinn, Noel
      - "Un Analisis del Planeamiento Educativo en Paraguay: Problemas y Perspectivas," n.d. (Folder 9)
      - "Data Sources and Information Available in Paraguay," 1978 (Folder 10)
      - "Estudios acerca del Funcionamiento del Sistema de Educacion del Paraguay"
        - No. 1. "Factores que Afectarian al Rendimiento Escolar en la Educacion Primaria del Paraguay," 1977 (Folder 11)
        - No. 2. "Examen Longitudinal de los Factores que Afectarian al Rendimiento Escolar," 1977 (Folder 12)
        - No. 4. "Analisis de los Componentes de Gastos en Dos Instituciones de Ensenanza Comercial," 1978 (Folder 13)
        - No. 5. "Caracteristicas de las Escuelas que Presentan un Flujo Irregular de Matricula de Primero a Segundo Grado de 9 a 10 Anos de Edad," 1978 (Folder 14)
      - "Final Report of Advisory Project of Harvard University to Office of Educational Planning, Ministry of Education, Paraguay," n.d. (Folder 15)
      - "Trip Report to Paraguay," n.d. (Folder 16)
    - McGinn, Noel, and Ernesto Schiefelbien, "How Educational Statistics Can Be Utilized for Policy Analysis: A Case Study," 1978 (Folder 17)
    - "Proposal to Establish Cooperative Program in Educational Planning with TA/EHR-Harvard Contract, USAID Mission in Paraguay and the Government of Paraguay," n.d. (Folder 18)
    - Schiefelbein, Ernesto, "Estimating Enrollment Flow Rates in Developing Countries: Repitiion [sic] in the Schools of Paraguay," 1978 (Folder 19)
    - Warwick, Donald P., "Strengthening Educational Planning in Paraguay: A Preliminary Report," n.d. (Folder 20)
    - Computer data printout (Box 12., Folder 1)
    - Miscellany (Folder 2)
  - Peru. Drysdale, Robert S., "Dynamics of Change in the Peruvian University System: A Study in the Politics of Higher Education," 1975
    - Chapter 1. "University and Society in Peru: Framework for Analysis" (Folder 3)
    - Chapter 2. "Historical Background" (Folder 4)
    - Chapter 6. "New Approach and the Limits of Policy, 1968-1975" (Folder 5)
  - Salvador
    - Anderson, Lascelles, "Rates of Return to Human Capital: A Test Using El Salvador Data," 1979 (Folder 6)
    - Barrios-Yaselly, Maritza, "Labor Force Structure, Income Distribution and Schooling: The Case of El Salvador," 1978 (Folder 7)
    - Davis, Russell G.
      - "Estructura, Funcionamiento y Tareas para ODEPOR," 1974 (Folder 8)
      - "Planning in the Ministry of Education of El Salvador: Organization and Planning Activity," 1979 1979 (Folder 9)
      - "A Study of Educational Relevance in El Salvador," 1979 (Box 13., Folder 1)
    - "Fundamentos Doctrinarios de la Reforma Educativa, 1968-1972," 1970 (Folder 2)
    - Harvard University. Center for Studies in Education and Development, "An Assessment of the Relevance of Education in El Salvador," 1977
      - Part 1. Introduction (Folder 3)
      - Part 2. "Four Studies of Educational Relevance in El Salvador" (Folder 4-6)
        - Section 1. "Worker/Employer Study: An Analytical Report"
        - Section 2. "Follow Up: The Assessment of the Relevance of the Diversified Bachillerato" (Folder 7-9)
        - Section 3. "Towards Relevance in Non-School Education in El Salvador: An Analysis of Audience Demand and Learning Sources" (Folder 10-11)
        - Section 4. "The Work-Force Study: A General Assessment of Relevance" (Box 14., Folder 1)
      - Part 3. "Appendix I: Statistical Procedures" (Folder 2)
      - Part 4. "A Summary of Conclusions" (Folder 3)
      - Miscellany (Folder 4)
    - Ishikawa, Eriko, "Education, Type of Marriage, and Fertility in El Salvador," n.d. (Folder 5)
    - Johnson, Ian, and Oliver Bloch, "Socio Economic Determinants of Fertility in El Salvador: Preliminary Report on Research Study," 1978 (Folder 6)
    - Lewis, Gary, "A Preliminary Report on the 1975 National Survey on Manpower and Demographic Aspects in El Salvador," 1977 (Folder 7)
    - McGinn, Noel, and Donald Warwick
      - "The Evolution of Educational Planning in El Salvador: A Case Study," 1978 (Folder 8)
      - "Sector Analysis in Education: A Case Study with Recommendations," 1978 (Folder 9)
    - Salvador. Ministerio de Educacion. Oficina de Planeamiento y Organizacion. "Analisis Sectorial de la Educacion en el Salvador"
      - Documentos Analiticos de Trabajo
        - No. 1. "Indicadores del Acceso a la Educacion, 1950-1971," 1974 (Folder 10)
        - No. 2. "Conclusiones sobre Repeticion, Desercion y Resultados de la Preuba Nacional en Educacion Basica," 1977 (Folder 11)
        - No. 2. Translation. "Conclusions about Repetition, Dropout and National Achievement Examination Results in Basic Education," 1977 (Folder 12)
        - No. 3. Translation. "Costs of Basic Education," 1977 (Folder 13)
        - No. 4. Translation. "Access to Basic Education School Facilities and Teaching Staff," 1977 (Folder 14)
        - No. 6. Translation. "The Relations of Social, Economic and Cultural Factors and National Achievement Exam Results," 1977 (Folder 15)
        - No. 8. Translation. "Analysis of the Answers Given by Students in the National Achievement Examinations," 1977 (Box 15., Folder 1)
        - No. 10. Translation. "Principal Findings, Priorities, Costs and Benefits of Policies Designed to Increase the Efficiency of Basic Education," 1977 (Folder 2)
        - No. 11. Translation. "Kindergarten," 1977 (Folder 3)
        - No. 12. "Bachillerato," 1977 (Folder 4)
        - No. 12. Translation. "Secondary Education," 1977 (Folder 5)
        - No. 13. Translation. "Higher Education," 1977 (Folder 6)
        - No. 15. Translation. "Estimates of the Availability of Resources for the Years 1986-2002 and Possible Combinations of Targets for Enrollment, Programs to Increase Efficiency and Programs to Improve Relevance of the Five Types of Educational and Training Activities," 1978 (Folder 7)
    - Salvador. Ministerio de Educacion. Oficina de Planeamiento y Organizacion, "Analisis Sectorial de la Educacion en el Salvador" (Contd.)
      - Documentos Estadisticos de Trabajo
        - No. 1. "Resultados Estadisticos de la Encuesta de Audencia: Muestreo por Cuotas," 1975 (Folder 8)
        - No. 2A. "Estimaciones de Matricula Inicial y Final y Estimaciones de los Resultados de las Pruebas Nacionales de la Educacion Basica: Sector Publico," 1976 (Folder 9)
        - No. 2B. "Estimaciones de Matricula Inicial y Final y Estimaciones de los Resultados de las Pruebas Nacionales de la Educacion Basica: Sector Privado," 1976 (Folder 10)
        - No. 2C. "Estimaciones de Matricula Inicial y Final y Estimaciones de los Resultados de las Pruebas Nacionales de la Educacion Basica: Cuadros Adicionales," 1976 (Folder 11)
        - No. 2D. "Estimaciones de Matricula Inicial, Repeticion y Perdidas de Matricula por Grado y Edad, y Estimaciones de Desaprobados y su Relacion con la Repeticion," 1976 (Folder 12)
        - No. 3. "Estimaciones de Resultados de la Prueba Nacional de los Estudiantes de Educacion Basica y Estimaciones de Factores Sociales, Economicos y Culturales de sus Hogares: Basadas en una Sub-Muestra de Estudiantes," n.d. (Folder 13)
        - No. 4A. "Calculos y Estimaciones de Insumos y Otras Caracteristicas Escolares de las Escuelas de Educacion Basica," 1976 (Box 16., Folder 1)
        - No. 5. "Estimaciones de los Costos de la Educacion Basica," n.d. (Folder 2)
        - No. 5A. "Estimaciones de los Costos de la Educacion Basica: Sector Publico," 1976 (Folder 3)
        - No. 5B. "Estimaciones de los Costos de la Educacion Basica: Sector Privado," 1976 (Folder 4)